Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Commercial Recordings Collection AIA.031.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: 33 1/3 RPM Records, circa 1951-1999; 752 sound discs
  - Gorman, Michael and Willy Clancy, Jigs, Reels and Hornpipes (Folkways FW 6819 ) (Disk XA33 673)
  - Graham, Davey, Duck Baker, Dave Evans and Dan Ar Bras, Irish Reels Jigs Hornpipes & Airs Arranged for the Guitar (Kicking Mule KM 157) (Disk XA33 687)
  - Graham, Len, Wind and Water (Topic 12TS334) (Disk XA33 182)
  - Greehy, Anne, Danny Boy and other Irish Favorites (Avoca 33-AV-137) (Disk XA33 79)
  - Greehy, Anne, My Own Dear Galway Bay (Avoca 33-ST-161) (Disk XA33 137)
  - Greehy, Anne with Jackie Roche, Ireland My Homeland (Avoca 33-AV-107) (Disk XA33 208)
  - Green Fields of America, Live in Concert (Green Linnet SIF 1096) (Disk XA33 580)
  - Green Grass Cloggers, Through the Ears (Rounder Rounder 0228) (Disk XA33 57)
  - Griffin, Vincent, Vincent Griffin, Traditional Fiddle Music from County Clare (Topic 12TS338) (Disk XA33 266)
  - Guard, Charles, Avenging and Bright (Shanachie 79014) (Disk XA33 636)
  - Guinchard, Rufus, Rufus Guinchard, Newfoundland Fiddler (Breakwater 1002) (Disk XA33 205)
  - Gunn Family, Gunns, Singing Family of Dublin (Delyse ECB 3143) (Disk XA33 297)
  - Hall, Tony, Fieldvole Music (Free Reed FRR 012) (Disk XA33 535)
  - Hammond, David, Belfast Street Songs (Request RLP8059) (Disk XA33 354)
  - Hanna, George and Sarah Anne O'Neill, On the Shores of Lough Neagh (Topic 12TS372) (Disk XA33 31)
  - Harte, Frank, And Listen To My Song (Mulligan RMLP 1013) (Disk XA33 20)
  - Harte, Frank, Daybreak and a Candle-End (Foetain SPIN 995) (Disk XA33 159)
  - Hayward, Richard with the Loyal Sons of William, Orange Sash (Fontana TFL 5069) (Disk XA33 83)
  - Healy, Skip, Empty Pockets (Meadowlark 104) (Disk XA33 146)
  - Healy, Tommy and Johnny Duffy, Memories of Sligo (Topic 12TS335) (Disk XA33 176)
  - Heaney, Joe, Joe Heaney (Philo 2004) (Disk XA33 154)
  - Heaney, Joe, Joe Heaney, Irish Traditional Songs in Gaelic and Irish (Topic 12T91) (Disk XA33 161)
  - Heaney, Joe and Gabe O'Sullivan, Joe and the Gabe, Songs and Music of Galway (Green Linnet SIF 1018) (Disk XA33 211)
  - Hebbert, Michael, Rampin' Cat (Free Reed FRR 009) (Disk XA33 410)
  - Henry, Noel, Peaceful Spot in Ireland (Rego REGO 002) (Disk XA33 34)
  - Hernon, P.J., P.J.Hernon (Gael-linn CEF.065) (Disk XA33 621)
  - Hickey, Billy and Ken Byrne, Two Irish Lads (Rego Irish Rego 003) (Disk XA33 147)
  - Highwoods String Band, Dance All Night (Rounder Rounder0045) (Disk XA33 581)
  - Highwoods Stringband, Fire on the Mountains (Rounder Rounder0023) (Disk XA33 372)
  - Highwoods Stringband, No. 3 Special (Rounder Rounder0071) (Disk XA33 373)
  - Hill 16, Hill 16 (Meadowlatk 101) (Disk XA33 427)
  - Hill, Noel and Tony Linnane, Noel Hill and Tony Linnane (Tara TARA 2006) (Disk XA33 148)
  - Hill, Noel and Tony McMahon, I gCnoc na Grai (Gael-linn CEF 114) (Disk XA33 23)
  - Hinchcliffe, Frank, In Sheffield Park (Topic 12TS308) (Disk XA33 409)
  - Holland, Jerry, Jerry Holland (Rounder 7008) (Disk XA33 265)
  - Holland, Lori, Irish Folk Songs for Women (Folkways FG 3518) (Disk XA33 184)
  - Holmes, Joe and Len Graham, Chaste Muses Bards and Sages, Traditional Songs, Ballads, Lilts and Fiddle Tunes from the North of Ireland (Free Reed FR007) (Disk XA33 241)
  - Horslips, Happy to Meet Sorry to Part (Oats MOO 3)
  - Horslips, Unfortunate Cup of Tea! (Oats MOO 8) (Disk XA33 376)
  - Houl Yer Whisht, On Boyne's Red Shore [No Jacket] (Outlet OAS 3005) (Disk XA33 46)
  - House Band, Word of Mouth (Green Linnet SIF 3045) (Disk XA33 426)
  - How to Change a Flat Tire, Traditional Music of Ireland and Shetland (Front Hall FHR-018) (Disk XA33 425)
  - Imlach, Hamish, Murdered Ballads (Transatlantic XTRA 1131) (Disk XA33 82)
  - Irish Balladeers, We Don't Mind if We Do..! (Avoca 33-ST-177) (Disk XA33 143)
  - Irish Balladeers, Once Upon a Time (Avoca 33-ST-203) (Disk XA33 458)
  - Irish Balladeers, Molly Maguires (Avoca 33-ST-162) (Disk XA33 562)
  - Irish Breakdown, In Sunshine or in Shadow (Wren WSLP005) (Disk XA33 718)
  - Irish Connection, Roll of Honour (Phoenix Rising Records BP-3560-A) (Disk XA33 725)
  - Irish Country Four, Songs, Ballads and Instrumental Tunes from Ulster (Topic 12TS209) (Disk XA33 115)
  - Irish Festival Singers, Feis Eireann (Angel ANG-65025) (Disk XA33 649)
  - Irish Festival Singers, Ballads and Folk Songs (Angel ANG-65016) (Disk XA33 650)
  - Irish Ramblers, Patriot Game (Elektra EKS-7249) (Disk XA33 461)
  - Irish Tradition, Catchin' the Tune, Vol. 1 (A.Y. Productions 4440) (Disk XA33 179)
  - Irish Tradition, Corner House (Green Linnet SIF 1016) (Disk XA33 702)
  - Irish Tradition, Times We've Had (Green Linnet SIF 1063) (Disk XA33 749)
  - Irvine, Andy, Rainy Sundays…Windy Dreams (Tara TARA 3002) (Disk XA33 223)
  - Jack Barrett Ceili Band, Jackie Hearst International Ceili Band, The Liberty Boys, Walls of Limerick and Other Ceili Favourites (ABC-Paramount ABC-471) (Disk XA33 325)
  - Jock Tamson's Bairns, Jock Tamson's Bairns (Temple TP 002) (Disk XA33 482)
  - Johnstons, Anthology (Transatlantic MTRA 2012) (Disk XA33 732)
  - Johnstons, Barley Corn (Transatlantic Records Ltd. TRA 185) (Disk XA33 663)
  - Johnstons, Bitter Green (Transatlantic TRA 211) (Disk XA33 734)
  - Johnstons, Colours of the Dawn (Vanguard VSD 6572) (Disk XA33 733)
  - Johnstons, Give a Damn (Transatlantic TRA 184) (Disk XA33 722)
  - Johnstons, Streets of London (Sonas SOLP 1004) (Disk XA33 459)
  - Johnstons, Travelling People (Marble Arch MAL 808) (Disk XA33 731)
  - Joyce, Jimmy, You Don't Have to Be Irish (MCA MCA-174) (Disk XA33 713)
  - JSD Band, Travelling Days (Warner Brothers BS 2723) (Disk XA33 298)
  - Keane, Dolores, There Was a Maid (Claddagh CC23) (Disk XA33 242)
  - Keane, Dolores and John Faulkner, Broken Hearted I'll Wander (Mulligan LUN 033) (Disk XA33 21)
  - Keane, Dolores and John Faulkner, Sail Og Rua (Green Linnet SIF 3033) (Disk XA33 174)
  - Keane, Dolores, John Faulkner and Eamonn Curran, Farewell to Eirinn, Music and Songs of Emigration from Ireland to America (Green Linnet SIF 3003) (Disk XA33 561)
  - Keane, James, Roll Away the Reel World (Green Linnet SIF 1026) (Disk XA33 51)
  - Keane, James, Irish Accordion of James Keane (Rex 808) (Disk XA33 536)
  - Keane, Sean, Gusty's Frolics (Claddagh CC17) (Disk XA33 267)
  - Keenan, Paddy, Paddy Keenan (Gael-linn CEF 045) (Disk XA33 292)
  - Kelly, Eamon, Stories From Ireland (Rego R-11000) (Disk XA33 448)
  - Kelly, James, Paddy O'Brien and Daithi Sproule, Spring in the Air (Shanachie 29018) (Disk XA33 180)
  - Kelly, John, John Kelly, Fiddle and Concertina Player (Topic 12TFR#504) (Disk XA33 181)
  - Kelly, John and James, John and James Kelly (Tara TARA 1008) (Disk XA33 222)
  - Kennedy, Frankie and Mairead Ni Mhaonaigh, Altan (Green Linnet SIF 1078) (Disk XA33 651)
  - Kennedy, Michael J., 65 Years of Irish Music (June Appal JA 019) (Disk XA33 123)
  - Kiley, John, He's Irish and He's Beautiful (JENA GMP 120) (Disk XA33 299)
  - Kilfenora Ceili Band, Clare Ceili (EMI 1013) (Disk XA33 41)
  - Kilfenora Ceili Band, Kilfenora Ceili Band (Souvenir SLP 904) (Disk XA33 98)
  - Kilfenora Ceili Band, Kilfenora Ceili Band (Transatlantic TRA283) (Disk XA33 356)
  - Kilfenora Fiddle Ceili Band, Irish Traditional Fiddle Music, Reels and Jigs (Everest 2120) (Disk XA33 194)
  - Killoran, Paddy, Paddy Killoran's Back in Town (Shanachie 33003) (Disk XA33 268)
  - Kimmel, John, Early Recordings of Irish Traditional Dance Music (Leader LED 2060) (Disk XA33 126)
  - Kimmel, John, Virtuoso of the Irish Accordion (Folkways RF 112) (Disk XA33 753)
  - Kincora Ceili Band, Gardiner Traditional Trio, Belhavel Trio, Ceol Tire (Comhaltas Ceoltoiri Eireann CL-12) (Disk XA33 193)
  - Kinnaird, Alison, Harp Key (Temple 011-TUS) (Disk XA33 243)
  - Kinnaird, Alison, Harper's Gallery (Temple TP003) (Disk XA33 244)
  - Kirkpatrick, John and Sue Harris, Among the Many Attractions at the Show Will Be a Really High Class Band (Topic 12TS295) (Disk XA33 245)
  - Knock-na-shee, Last Night's Fun (Shanachie 29017) (Disk XA33 270)
  - Kornog, Ar Seizh Avel, On Seven Winds (Green Linnet SIF 1062) (Disk XA33 246)
  - Kornog, Premiere, Music from Brittany (Green Linnet SIF 1055) (Disk XA33 397)
  - Kretzner, Leo, Jay Leibovitz and Friends, Pigtown Fling Dulcimer Sessions (Green Linnet SIF1019) (Disk XA33 592)
  - Laney, Bill, Bill Laney, Classic Recordings of Scottish Fiddling (Shanachie 14002) (Disk XA33 247)
  - Lauder, Sir Harry, Scotch Songs (Everest/Scala SC-877) (Disk XA33 716)
  - Lenihan, Tom, Paddy's Panacea (Topic 12TS363) (Disk XA33 33)
  - Little Gaelic Singers, From Donegal to Galway Bay with the Little Gaelic Singers (Decca DL 8435) (Disk XA33 615)
  - Living Strings, When Irish Eyes Are Smiling (RCA Camden CAS 859) (Disk XA33 484)
  - Living Voices, Living Voices Sing Irish Songs (RCA Camden CAS 665) (Disk XA33 483)
  - Logan, Al with Paddy Noonan and His Band, If We Only Had Old Ireland Over Here (Rego Irish 3000) (Disk XA33 641)
  - Lomax, Alan ed., Irish Folk Songs (Columbia SL 204) (Disk XA33 135)
  - Ludlows, Wind and the Sea (Pye NPL 18150) (Disk XA33 284)
  - Lundy, Emmett W., Fiddle Tunes from Grayson County, Virginia (String STR 802) (Disk XA33 119)
  - Mabus, Joel, Fairies and Fools (Flying Fish FF 296) (Disk XA33 389)
  - MacBee, Hamper, Cumberland Moonshiner (Prestige Folklore FL14008) (Disk XA33 741)
  - Mac Donnchadha, Sean, Padraic O Cathain and Tomas O Neachtain, More Grand Airs from Connemara (Topic 12T202) (Disk XA33 307)
  - Mac Donnchadha, Sean, Padraic O Cathain and Tomas O Neachtain, Grand Airs of Connemara (Topic 12TS177) (Disk XA33 167)
  - Mac Mathuna, Ciaran, Mo Cheol Thu (Gael-linn CEF 064) (Disk XA33 70)
  - Macalla, Mna na hEireann (Gael-linn CEF 110) (Disk XA33 480)
  - MacColl, Ewan and Peggy Seeger, Classic Scots Ballads (Transatlantic XTRA 1054) (Disk XA33 78)
  - Mackenzie, Carl, Celtic Ceilidh (World CLM 1006) (Disk XA33 47)
  - Mackenzie, Carl, "…And His Sound Is Cape Breton" (CLM WRC1-1548) (Disk XA33 338)
  - MacKenzie, Tom, Finally Tuned (Rooster 104) (Disk XA33 280)
  - MacMahon, Dolly, Dolly (Claddagh CC3) (Disk XA33 212)
  - MacNeill, Finlay, Fonn is Furan, A Tune and Welcome (Temple TP009) (Disk XA33 248)
  - Makem, Tommy, Lonesome Waters (Shanachie 52011) (Disk XA33 10)
  - Makem, Tommy, Tommy Makem Sings Tommy Makem (Columbia CS 9545) (Disk XA33 18)
  - Makem, Tommy and Liam Clancy, Two For the Early Dew (Blackbird BLB 1007) (Disk XA33 521)
  - Malachy Doris and His Ceili Band with Peter Sherry, Dancin' Irishman (Fiesta FLPS 1558) (Disk XA33 239)
  - Malachy Doris Ceili Band and Pete Sherry, Irish Night Out (Major Minor MCP5056) (Disk XA33 281)
  - Martin Mulvihill School, Irish Music: The Living Tradition (Innisfree/Green Linnet SIF 1009) (Disk XA33 667)
  - Martin, Denis, Irish Sing-Along (London TW91234) (Disk XA33 315)
  - McAloon, Sean and John Rea, Drops of Brandy (Topic 12TS287) (Disk XA33 296)
  - McBride, Owen, Owen McBride (Philo 1005) (Disk XA33 186)
  - McBee, Hamper, Raw Mash: Songs and Stories of Hamper McBee (Rounder Records 61) (Disk XA33 724)
  - McCaffrey, Leo, Typical Irishman (Release BRL 4054) (Disk XA33 616)
  - McClatchy, Debby, Homemade Goodies (Philo 106) (Disk XA33 583)
  - McClatchy, Debby, Lady Luck (Innisfree/Green Linnet SIF1017) (Disk XA33 584)
  - McComiskey, Billy, Makin' the Rounds (Green Linnet SIF 1034) (Disk XA33 545)
  - McConnell, Cathal, On Lough Erne's Shore (Topic 12TS377) (Disk XA33 548)
  - McConnell, Cathal and Robin Morton, Irish Jubilee (Topic 12T290) (Disk XA33 549)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack Sings Irish Songs (Pickwick CAS 407) (Disk XA33 136)
  - McCormack, John, Art of John McCormack (EMI EX2900563) (Disk XA33 349)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack Concert (Avoca 33-ST-112) (Disk XA33 350)
  - McCormack, John, Song O' My Heart (The John McCormack Assaciation of Greater Kansas City, Inc. ) (Disk XA33 351)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack Sings Irish Songs (RCA Camden CAS-407(e)) (Disk XA33 481)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack (Everest/Scala SC-820) (Disk XA33 498)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack, Volume VI, Love Serenades (Everest/Scala SC-889) (Disk XA33 500)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack (Everest/Scala 853) (Disk XA33 501)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack, Volume V, Songs of Romance (Everest/Scala SC-882) (Disk XA33 503)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack Sings a Treasury of Irish Melodies (Arabesque 8124) (Disk XA33 504)
  - McCormack, John, Recital (Rubini GV523) (Disk XA33 505)
  - McCormack, John, Irish Minstrel (RCA ARM1-4997) (Disk XA33 506)
  - McCormack, John, Sacred Music (RCA Camden CAL-635) (Disk XA33 507)
  - McCormack, John, True Redeemer of Bel Canto, Vol. V (Opal 833/4) (Disk XA33 508)
  - McCormack, John, Popular Songs and Irish Ballads (EMI EX 29 0007 3) (Disk XA33 509)
  - McCormack, John, Light of Other Days (Pearl GEMM 274/5) (Disk XA33 510)
  - McCormack, John, Voice for all Seasons, Vol. VI (Opal 841/2) (Disk XA33 511)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack, Volume IV, Irish Songs (Everest/Scala SC-873) (Disk XA33 512)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack Sings Arias and Art Songs (Arabesque 8105-2) (Disk XA33 513)
  - McCormack, John, John McCormack in Opera (Delta TQD 3009) (Disk XA33 516)
  - McCormack, John, Great John McCormack Sings Irish Songs and Traditional Melodies (Murray Hill S-4359) Five discs (Disk XA33 618)
  - McCormack, John and Enrico Caruso, Enrico Caruso, John McCormack (Egmont EGM 7015) (Disk XA33 514)
  - McCormack, John and Enrico Caruso, Antique (Hudson 225) (Disk XA33 515)
  - McCormick, John, John McCormick sings Panis Angelicus (Pearl GEMM 176 E) (Disk XA33 50)
  - McCullough, L. E., His Own Kind (Wildebeest WB008) (Disk XA33 285)
  - McCusker Brothers Ceili Band, Irish Country Dances (Avoca 33-AV-138) (Disk XA33 192)
  - McCutcheon, John, Wind That Shakes the Barley (June Appal JA014) (Disk XA33 585)
  - McDermott, Josie, Darby's Farewell (Topic 12TS325) (Disk XA33 550)
  - McDermott, Kevin and Ralph Richey, Music from the Works of James Joyce (Sunphone SP001) (Disk XA33 185)
  - McDonagh, Owen and the Bogside Men, Songs of Irish Civil Rights (Musidisc SM 3517) (Disk XA33 720)
  - McGann, Andy and Paddy Reynolds, Andy McGann and Paddy Reynolds (Shanachie 29004) (Disk XA33 273)
  - McGann, Andy and Paul Brady, Andy McGann and Paul Brady (Shanachie 29009) (Disk XA33 272)
  - McGettigan, John and his Irish Minstels, Classic Recordings of Irish Traditional Music in America (Topic Records 12T367) (Disk XA33 729)
  - McGinley, Danny, In Our Time (Bunnan Bui Bui-001) (Disk XA33 203)
  - McGlinchey, Brendan, Music of a Champion (Silver Hill PSH100) (Disk XA33 262)
  - McGonigle, Mary, Memories of Ireland (MGD MGD 10178) (Disk XA33 178)
  - McGonigle, Mary, Going Back to Ireland (MGD MGD 10177) (Disk XA33 217)
  - McGreevy, Johnny and Seamus Cooley, McGreevy & Cooley (Philo PH 2005) (Disk XA33 692)
  - McGuire, Seamus and Manus, Humours of Lisadell (Folk-Legacy FSE 78) (Disk XA33 120)
  - McKenna, Joe and Antoinette, Farewell to Fine Weather (Shanachie 79043) (Disk XA33 274)
  - McKenna, Joe and Antoinette, At Home (Shanachie 29016) (Disk XA33 442)
  - McKenna, Joe and Antoinette, Joe and Antoinette McKenna, Traditional Music of Ireland -Irsih Pipes and Harp (Shanachie 29011) (Disk XA33 689)
  - McMahon, Tommy and Bernard O'Sullivan, Clare Concertinas (Topic/Free Reed 12TFRS502) (Disk XA33 623)
  - McMahon, Tony, Tony McMahon, Sean O Duibhir a'ghleanna, the Wounded Huzzar, an Buachaillin Bua agus Ceolta Eile (Gael-linn CEF 033) (Disk XA33 625)
  - McMahon, Tony, Tony McMahon (Gael-linn CEF 033) (Disk XA33 710)
  - McNulty Family, Irish Showboat (Coral CRL57368) (Disk XA33 328)
  - McNulty Family, Twelve Authentic Irish Folk Songs (Colonial LP 621) (Disk XA33 502)
  - McNulty, Pat, Pat McNulty, Uilleann Pipes (Silver Hill P.S.H. 103) (Disk XA33 202)
  - McPeake Family, Irish Traditional Folk Songs and Music (Topic 12T87) (Disk XA33 68)
  - McPeake Family, Irish to be Sure (Wind Mill WMD 151) (Disk XA33 249)
  - Men of No Property, This is Free Belfast (Paredon P1006) (Disk XA33 56)
  - Mickey Griffin's Shamrock Orchestra, Favorite Irish Dances (Colonial COL. LP-225) (Disk XA33 279)
  - Miller, Rodney and Randy, Castles in the Air (Fretless FR 119) (Disk XA33 388)
  - Mitchell, Pat, Uilleann Pipes (Topic 12TS294) (Disk XA33 348)
  - Molloy, Matt, Stony Steps (Green Linnet SIF 3041) (Disk XA33 14)
  - Molloy, Matt, Matt Molloy (Green Linnet SIF 3008) (Disk XA33 553)
  - Molloy, Matt and Sean Keane, Contentment is Wealth (Green Linnet SIF 1058) (Disk XA33 559)
  - Molloy, Matt, Paul Brady and Tommy Peoples, Matt Molloy, Paul Brady, Tommy Peoples (Green Linnett SIF 3018) (Disk XA33 691)
  - Molly Maguires, Irish Balladeers (Avoca 33-ST-162) (Disk XA33 738)
  - Moloney, Mick, Mick Moloney Test Pressing (Green Linnet ) (Disk XA33 81)
  - Moloney, Mick, Mick Moloney Test Pressing (Green Linnet ) (Disk XA33 99)
  - Moloney, Mick, There Were Roses Test Pressing (Green Linnet SIF 1057) (Disk XA33 105)
  - Moloney, Mick, Moloney Test Pressing (Label and catalog # not listed ) (Disk XA33 132)
  - Moloney, Mick, We Have Met Together (Guinvarda GS-11.163) (Disk XA33 357)
  - Moloney, Mick, We Have Met Together [No disk] (Transatlantic TRA 263) (Disk XA33 606)
  - Moloney, Mick, Strings Attached (Green Linnet SIF 1027) (Disk XA33 698)
  - Moloney, Mick, There Were Roses [Test pressing] (Green Linnet SIF 1057) (Disk XA33 84)
  - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, Uncommon Bonds (Green Linnet SIF 1053) (Disk XA33 87)
  - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, Mick Moloney with Eugene O'Donnell (Green Linnet SIF 1010) (Disk XA33 693)
  - Moloney, Mick, Jimmy Keane, RobbieO'Connell and Liz Carroll, There Were Roses (Green Linnet SIF1057) (Disk XA33 709)
  - Moloney, O'Connell and Keane, Kilkelly (Green Linnet SIF1072) (Disk XA33 690)
  - Moloney, Paddy and Sean Potts, Tin Whistles (Claddagh CC 15) (Disk XA33 537)
  - Moonlighters, Moonlighters Sing Irish Folk Hits (Shamrock Souvenir Harp 2) (Disk XA33 324)
  - Moore, Barry, Treaty Stone (Mulligan LUN 022) (Disk XA33 177)
  - Moore, Christy, Prosperous (Tara TARA 1001) (Disk XA33 173)
  - Moore, Christy, Spirit of Freedom (WEA IR0840) (Disk XA33 213)
  - Moore, Christy, Ordinary Man (Green Linnet SIF 3301) (Disk XA33 660)
  - Moore, Christy, Ride On (WEA IR 0407) (Disk XA33 694)
  - Moore, Christy, Time Has Come (WEA 24-0150-1) (Disk XA33 707)
  - Moore, Christy, Donal Lunny and Jimmy Faulkner, Live in Dublin (Tara TARA 2005) (Disk XA33 661)
  - Morrissey, Ruthie, Sings the Irish Soldier Boy (Avoca 33-AV-127) (Disk XA33 35)
  - Moving Hearts, Moving Hearts (WEA IR 58387) (Disk XA33 478)
  - Muintir Lewis, Weeds in the Garden (Tara 2003) (Disk XA33 59)
  - Mulcahy, Mick, Mick Mulcahy (Gael-linn CEF 050) (Disk XA33 538)
  - Mulvany, Maeve, Irish Rebel Ballads (Rex RLP-772) (Disk XA33 730)
  - Mulvihill, Martin and Mick Moloney, Traditional Irish Fiddling from County Limerick (Green Linnet SIF 1012) (Disk XA33 106)
  - Mulvihill, Tommy, Emerald Roots (Rego Irish 15000) (Disk XA33 594)
  - Mulvihill. Brendan, Flax in Bloom (Green Linnet SIF 1020) (Disk XA33 703)
  - Murphy, Dennis and Julia Clifford, Star Above the Garter (Claddagh CC5) (Disk XA33 343)
  - Murphy, Rose, Milltown Lass, Old Time Irish Fiddle and Accordion (Topic 12TS316) (Disk XA33 151)
  - Murray, Ruby, Irish (and Proud Of It) (Capitol ST 10327) (Disk XA33 642)
  - Na Fili, Chanter's Tune (Transatlantic TRA 353) (Disk XA33 563)
  - Na Fili, …A Kindly Welcome (Dolphin DOL. 1008) (Disk XA33 566)
  - Ni Dhomhnaill, Mairead, Ni Dhomhnaill, Mairead (Gael-linn CEF 055) (Disk XA33 29)
  - Ni Dhomhnaill, Triona, Triona (Green Linnet SIF 3034) (Disk XA33 141)
  - Ni Dhomhnaill, Triona, Triona (Gael-linn CEF.043) (Disk XA33 142)
  - Ni Ghuairim, Sorcha, Sorcha ni Ghuairim Sings Traditional Irish Songs (Folkways FW6861) (Disk XA33 188)
  - Ni Mhaonaigh, Mairead and Frankie Kennedy, Ceol Aduaidh (Gael-linn CEF102) (Disk XA33 40)
  - Noonan, Paddy, Paddy Noonan Irish Party (Rego Irish R 20,000) (Disk XA33 290)
  - Noonan, Paddy, Musical Taste of Ireland (Peters International PLD 2063) (Disk XA33 303)
  - Noonan, Paddy, Live Irish Party at the Barleycorn (Ambassador TS-86) (Disk XA33 321)
  - Noonan, Paddy with Martin Mulhaire, Memories of Ireland Featuring Paddy Noonan and Martin Mulhaire (Request SRLP 10087) (Disk XA33 293)
  - Noonan. Paddy, Grand Irish Party (LSS Tifton T 60) (Disk XA33 617)
  - Novick, Billy and Guy Van Duser, New Pennywhistle Album (Innisfree/Green Linnet SIF 1013) (Disk XA33 539)
  - O Beaglaoich, Seamus agus Maire, Ciarraioch Mallaithe (Gael-linn CEFS037) (Disk XA33 595)
  - O Briain, Donncha, Donncha O Briain (Gael-linn CEF.083) (Disk XA33 379)
  - O Carra, Padraig agus Comhluadar, Abhan Trireach (Gael-linn CEF.059) (Disk XA33 378)
  - O Cathain, Darach, Darach O Cathain (Gael-linn CEF 040) (Disk XA33 30)
  - O Domhnallain, Tomas, Buntus Cainte: Lessons 1-60 (Gael-linn CT 5/6) Two discs (Disk XA33 88)
  - O Domhnallain, Tomas, Buntus Cainte: Lessons 61-130 (Gael-linn CT 7/8) Two discs (Disk XA33 89)
  - O Duibheannaigh, Aodh, Aodh O Duibheannaigh (Gael-linn CEF048) (Disk XA33 601)
  - O Riada, Sean, Our Musical Heritage (RTE FR 001/002/003) Three discs (Disk XA33 157)
  - O Riada, Sean, O Riada sa Gaiety le Sean O Se agus Ceoltoiri Cualann (Gael-linn CEF027) (Disk XA33 645)
  - O Riada, Sean, Mise Eire (Gael-linn CEF080) (Disk XA33 646)
  - O Se, Sean agus Ceoltoiri Cualann, O Riada sa Gaiety (Gael-linn CEF 027) (Disk XA33 130)
  - O'Brien, Paddy and Daithi Sproule, Stranger at the Gate (Green Linnet SIF 1091) (Disk XA33 540)
  - O'Brien, Thomas and Anne Greehy with Jackie Roche and His Orchestra, Irish Songs You Love (Avoca 33-AV-105) (Disk XA33 688)
  - O'Brien, Thomas and Ed Flaherty, Irish Tenors Sing Irish Favorites (Irish Musical Industries IMI-2503) (Disk XA33 613)
  - O'Connell, Robbie, Love of the Land (Green Linnet SIF 1097) (Disk XA33 532)
  - O'Connell, Robbie, Close to the Bone (Green Linnet SIF 1038) (Disk XA33 682)
  - O'Connor, Martin, Connachtman's Rambles (Mulligan LUN 027) (Disk XA33 541)
  - O'Dea, Michael, Danny Boy, Galway Bay, Rose of Tralee, Mother Macree and Other Itish Favourites (Rego Irish 17000) (Disk XA33 326)
  - O'Donnell, Al, Al O'Donnell (Trailer LER 2073) (Disk XA33 139)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene and James MacCafferty, Foggy Dew (Green Linnet SIF 1084) (Disk XA33 263)
  - O'Dowd, Barry and the Shamrock Singers, 20 Irish Party Songs (K-Tel NC 422) (Disk XA33 608)
  - O'Dowda, Brendan, World of Percy French (Columbia 1466) (Disk XA33 76)
  - O'Driscoll, Treasa with Micheal O Domhnaill, Farewell but Whenever, Love Songs of Ireland from the Fifteenth to the Twentieth Centuries (Gael-linn CEF 088) (Disk XA33 250)
  - O'Flynn, Liam, Brendan Voyage (Tara Tara 3006) (Disk XA33 278)
  - O'Halloran Brothers, Men of the Island (Topic 12TS305) (Disk XA33 604)
  - O'Hara, Mary, Love Songs of Ireland (Beltona LBE 20) (Disk XA33 28)
  - O'Hara, Mary, Traditional Irish Folk Songs (Everest FS 344) (Disk XA33 138)
  - O'Hara, Mary, Songs of Erin (London LL 1572) (Disk XA33 251)
  - O'Hara, Mary, Songs of Ireland (Tradition TLP 1024) (Disk XA33 252)
  - Oisin, Bealoideas (Tara 2011) (Disk XA33 564)
  - Old Swan Band, No Reels (Free Reed FRR011) (Disk XA33 591)
  - O'Leary, Johnny, Music for the Set, Music from Sliabh Luachra Vol. 5 (Topic 12TS357) (Disk XA33 152)
  - Oriel, Songs and Tunes of South East Ulster (Eagran MD 0001) (Disk XA33 565)
  - Oro Damhnaigh, Oro Damhnaigh (Gael-linn CEF056) (Disk XA33 602)
  - Oskay, Billy and Micheal O Domhnaill, Nightnoise (Windham Hill WH-1031) (Disk XA33 603)
  - Ossian, Dove Across the Water (Iona IR 004) (Disk XA33 568)